<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CompassLogger</string>

    <string name="title_section1">Info</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Feedback</string>

    <string name="ok">Agree</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>

    <string name="agreement_title">Consent to Participate in Research</string>
    <string name="agreement_message">
        The purpose of this study is to examine whether we can accurately predict certain types of
        demographic information and the daily routines of smartphone users using innocuous sensor
        data, such as from the accelerometer and compass.\n\n

        If you agree to be in this study, this app will ask you several questions about your
        demographics and daily routines. This app will then run in the background for one week.
        During this time, the app will periodically take snapshots of your smartphone\'s sensor data,
        to see whether any of it correlates with your survey responses. After one week, the app will
        uninstall itself and you will be granted the bonus payment. This app will run silently,
        will not collect any information that personally identifies you, and will not impact your
        phone\'s performance or battery life.

        Participation in this study will involve a total of 5 minutes to fill out the form, and then
        leaving the app running in the background for one week.\n\n

        This research will not benefit you directly, however it will indirectly benefit you and other
        smartphone users by helping system designers better understand what types of inferences
        could be made from sensor data.\n\n

        Some of the research questions may make you uncomfortable or upset. You are free to decline
        to stop the study at any time. You may also uninstall the app at any time to stop the study.
        All study data will be collected anonymously; at no point will we collect study data that
        identifies you personally.\n\n

        Your study data will be handled as confidentially as possible. If results of this study are
        published or presented, individual names and other personally identifiable information will
        not be used unless you give explicit permission for this below.\n\n

        The research data will be maintained for possible use in future research by myself or others.
        The same measures described above will be taken to protect confidentiality of this study data.\n\n

        Participants will be given $0.25 upon installing the app. Upon completing the study after one
        week, participants will be granted a $2.00 bonus.\n\n

        You have the right to decline to participate or to withdraw at any point in this study without
        penalty or loss of benefits to which you are otherwise entitled.\n\n

        If you have any questions or concerns about your rights and treatment as a research subject,
        you may contact the office of UC Berkeley\'s Committee for the Protection of Human
        Subjects, at 510-642-7461 or subjects@berkeley.edu.

    </string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact
        based on your message history
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">John Smith</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Add friends to messages</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Always</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>
    <string name="title_activity_form">FormActivity</string>
</resources>
