<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CompassLogger</string>

    <string name="title_section1">Info</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Feedback</string>

    <string name="agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>

    <string name="agreement_title">Consent to Participate in Research\n Understanding Smartphone Sensors</string>
    <string name="agreement_message">
        My name is Manar Safi. I am an undergraduate student working with Irwin Reyes and Serge
        Egelman in the Computer Science Department at the University of California, Berkeley.
        We are planning to conduct a research study, which I invite you to take part in.\n\n

        The purpose of this study is to examine whether we can accurately predict certain types of
        demographic information and the daily routines of smartphone users using innocuous sensor
        data, such as that from the accelerometer and compass.\n\n

        After downloading this app, if you agree to be in this study, you will be directed to a
        survey that will prompt you with several questions about your demographics and daily routines.
        This app will then run in the background for one week. During this time, the app will
        periodically take snapshots of your smartphone\'s sensor data (accelerometer, gyroscope,
        compass, GPS, battery state, proximity, and brightness) up to once every 30 minutes, which we
        will then use to determine whether any of it correlates with your survey responses. These
        measurements will be sent to our encrypted database. After one week, the app will prompt you to
        uninstall it, and you will be granted the bonus payment. This app will run silently, will not
        collect any information that personally identifies you other than GPS, and will not impact your
        phone\'s performance or battery life.

        Participation in this study will involve a total of 5 minutes to complete the survey, and then
        leaving the app running in the background for one week.\n\n

        This research will not benefit you directly. However, it will indirectly benefit you and other
        smartphone users by helping system designers better understand what types of inferences
        could be made from sensor data.\n\n

        Some of the research questions may make you uncomfortable or upset. You are free to decline
        to answer and stop the study at any time. You may also uninstall the app at any time to stop
        the study.\n\n

        The risks for this study are minimal: these involve a potential breach of confidentiality for
        GPS data and other location data. We will encrypt data to decrease the probability of such a
        breach.\n\n

        Your study data will be handled as confidentially as possible. This involves storage on encrypted
        databases and encrypted computers. If results of this study are published or presented, individual
        names and other personally identifiable information will not be used.\n\n

        The research data will be maintained for possible use in future research by myself or others.
        The same measures described above will be taken to protect confidentiality of this study data.\n\n

        You will be given $0.25 upon installing the app and entering your MTurk ID. Upon completing the
        study after one week, you will be granted a $2.00 bonus. This app will use some background data
        transfer, but should incur no more than 2MB of data transfered in the one week period.\n\n

        You have the right to decline to participate or to withdraw at any point in this study without
        penalty or loss of benefits to which you are otherwise entitled.\n\n

        If you have any questions or concerns about this study, you may contact Serge Egelman at
        egelman@cs.berkeley.edu.\n\n

        If you have any questions or concerns about your rights and treatment as a research subject,
        you may contact the office of UC Berkeley\'s Committee for the Protection of Human
        Subjects, at 510-642-7461 or subjects@berkeley.edu.\n\n

        CPHS# 2015-11-8097

    </string>


    <!-- For the Permission Denied dialog-->
    <string name="denied_permission_response">
        You chose to deny permissions that this app needs to collect data.\n
        Please recall that the app will not collect any personally identifiable information besides GPS. All data
        that is collected will be stored securely.\n\n

        <b>Please note: You will not be paid the $2.00 bonus without participating in this portion of the study.</b>\n\n

        The app will now close. If this is a mistake, you may restart the app and accept the permissions.
    </string>

    <string name="denied_permission_title">Permissions Denied Warning</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>

    <string name="survey_form_message">
        You will now be directed to complete a short survey for some demographic information needed for this research.
        As always, your data will be kept securely and confidentially.\n\n

        <b>Please note: You will not be paid the $2.00 bonus without participating in this portion of the study.</b>\n\n
    </string>

    <!-- For the survey form prompt dialog-->
    <string name="survey_form_title">Required Survey Form</string>

    <string name="survey_form_response">formResponse</string>


    <!-- For the deadline notification uninstall prompt dialog-->
    <string name="uninstall_message_title">Sensory Privacy Research Complete!</string>
    <string name="uninstall_message">
        Thank you for participating in our research project! \n\n
        One week has passed since you installed our app, so you are officially done with your participation.
        You can now proceed to uninstall the app.
    </string>
    <string name="uninstall_proceed_button">Proceed to Uninstall</string>

    <!-- For the MainActivity layout-->
    <string name="info">This app is for a study at UC Berkeley to better understand smartphone sensors.
        This application will log various sensor data over the course of one week.
    </string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact
        based on your message history
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">John Smith</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Add friends to messages</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Always</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>
    <string name="title_activity_form">FormActivity</string>

    <!-- Firebase settings -->
    <string name="firebase_url">https://sensorinference-xgymkq5nno.firebaseio.com/</string>
    <string name="gdocs_url">https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1rvRzCKcWDC-w6WKSMMpU8ZfljdOdOLXArqG1vVhFKeQ/viewform?entry.1826764866=</string>

    <!-- ACRA crash reporting settings -->
    <string name="error_not_init">Firebase connection not initialized</string>

    <!-- Auto-generated Git version DO NOT EDIT -->
    <string name="app_version">1948974</string>

</resources>
